rentokil-initial.com 2012-05-19

# Rentokil Initial - Privacy Policy - Rentokil Initial

**The Rentokil Initial Group* respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it. We encourage you to read this policy before using this site as your use of the site signifies that you agree with all of its terms.**

* Unless otherwise specified, references in this Privacy Policy to the Rentokil Initial Group, means Rentokil Initial plc and its group of companies.

This policy applies to personal information we hold about individuals. It does not apply to information we hold about companies and other organisations.

Browsing of our websites and most other services provided through our websites does not require the provision of any personal information. However, where you freely provide personal information about yourself, then by providing such information you signify your consent to our collecting and using your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We will only collect personal data from you to enable us to respond to a query or to provide a service that has been requested, or a service provided by one of our companies which we think may interest you.

We may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of internet browsers you use or the website from which you linked to our web site. You cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on this website.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. Upon request we will remove any subscriber (and related information) from our database.

Except as set out above, we will not pass on your details to anyone outside the Rentokil Initial Group without your permission. Since we operate globally, the information you submit may be transferred anywhere globally within our group of companies. We take reasonable precautions to ensure that this and all other transmissions will remain secure and under our control. Where you provide personal information you consent to such transmission.

This web site uses a web browser feature called a ‘cookie’. Cookies are files that your web browser places on your computer's hard drive. These are a recognised way of identifying you each time you return to the site so that you do not have to re–enter your personal details. You can find out more about the way cookies work on [wikipedia.org ](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie "HTTP Cookie on Wikipedia"). Most browsers allow you to turn off the cookies. In order to do this you should access the help menu on your browser, however this may restrict the web based services that you can use.

This website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware the Rentokil Initial Group is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other such sites and accordingly assumes no responsibility whatsoever in respect of such web sites.

For more information about our privacy policy please contact us at [dpofficer@rentokil-initial.com](mailto:dpofficer@rentokil-initial.com "Use your default mail program to email dpofficer@rentokil-initial.com").
